Wow!
Yoko, I can't see you at all.
You can't see her at all.
I'm not very good at food reporting.
Hello everyone, this is Kyoko Saito.
I'm here in Harajuku today.
Yay! Harajuku!
I've always wanted to get to know the 4th term student who recently joined Hinatazaka,
Today, I would like to have a sister date with Yoko Matsubaradera, a 4th term student, in Harajuku while wearing twin coordinates.
Yay!
Now, where are they?
Oh, there she is! There she is! Good morning!
Nice to meet you today.
I'm Yoko Uehara-ji.
I am Yoko Matsubaradera, a 4th year student.
Nice to meet you. I'm so happy!
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
Here's how we're coordinating today.
Wait a minute, it's hard to project.
It was so hard to show it.
The shoes are the same.
Our shoes are the same.
And their clothes are the same color.
They are different colors.
I'm so happy!
Well, let's get going.
Let's go.
Wow! It's so Harajuku!
Yoko, when was the last time you went to Harajuku?
I haven't been since I was in the 5th grade of elementary school.
A long time ago?
Yes, about 5 or 6 years ago.
I see. So this is your second time?Oh, yeah. So this is your second time then?
Yes, that's right.
I've been around here so long that I didn't really see much of it.
I see. So you came to Harajuku at night.
That's right. It was pretty sparkling.
Was it sparkling?
It was sparkling.
Today was Harajuku in the daytime.
I am glad to see so many people.
I used to go to Harajuku with Shu-san.
Wow!
That's right. I've been there a lot.
But, you know, things have changed a bit.
Really?
Maybe things are a little different from back then.
But today, I'm going to trust you and do my best.
Leave it to me.
Wow, even at this price, it only takes about two bottles.
I understand.
I'm glad.
Oh, wow!
Aren't these potatoes amazing?
This is amazing. I've never seen them before.
I've never seen them either.
I want to try them.
Let's try them.
Let's try some.
Let's go in.
I'm so excited. This is it, right?
This is what we're getting?
Looks delicious.
It looks delicious.
It's amazing.
Wow!
Wow!Amazing!!!
It's amazing.
It's so long.
It smells great.
Really?
Wow.
Amazing.
What a surprise.
Mine is butter soy sauce,
Yoko's is Gosham.
Barbecue.
Ah, barbecue.
It's delicious.
It tastes like barbecue sauce.
Does it taste completely different?
What should I make?
I don't know.
It's very nice and salty,
It's the most delicious.
So this is Harajuku.
This is Harajuku?
There's a great word of wisdom.
You want some of this?
Are you sure?
Yes, it's okay. Yes, it's good.
It's delicious.
Oh, I got it.
Bon appétit.
It's good, right?
Delicious! Here you go!
Bon appétit.
Barbecue flavor?
It's barbecue flavor.
It's very strong, isn't it?
It's delicious, isn't it?Delicious, isn't it?
It's so good!
It was so good! It was great!
Long Longer Longer Longer Guest! I have a sweet tooth!
Oh, my God! What's this? Another famous candy!
I think I've never seen one in the flesh!
Rainbow Watter candy!
The entrance is so cute! Cool!
The cutest little store!
Smells so good! Smells so sweet!
Wait! I can't hear the song "Hinatazaka" playing!
The song "Don't Open the Windows on Hyugaizaka" is playing in the store!
Oh, my gosh! How is this possible?
I feel like I'm going to start singing!
I can dance to it now!
I've seen it on TV.
It happens all the time!
Thank you!
Oh, my God! I can't see!
What's that?
It's unbelievably big! It's like this!
Oh, my God! Umbrella! Umbrella!
It's so big!
Where should I eat it from?
I can't see anything, Yoroko!
I can't see it at all!
Which way is the best way to eat it?
Oh, sure!
From the bottom...
From the purple?
Bon appétit!
It's sweet to the touch!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my gosh!
What does it taste like?
So sweet!Sweet!
I'm not very good at food report!
I don't know what it tastes like, but it's really good!
I love it! I can eat both salty and sweet!
I'm so happy!
Harajuku is the best!
Kyoko, do you have a favorite color?
I like pink, white and black.
Hmmm...
You're a blue girl, aren't you?
Yes, I like blue.
So you like cold and warm colors?
Oh, it's the other way around.
That's exactly how I feel about your outfit today.
That's for sure.
Thank you for the food.
I have an image of things for sale.
That's for sure.
I'd like to stop by a general store or something.
Is there anything?
Let's ask Kyoko-san, who knows the area well.
Wait a minute.
It's pretty unusual.
I'd like to buy something matching.
That's a good idea.
I have something really cute.
Oh, here.
Oh, you see this one here?
It's so cute.
Let's find some matching ones.
Let's find some.
Dumplings, dumplings, dumplings...
For Kugu-chan.
I want to buy carrots for Nibu-chan.
That's niceThat's good.
Bread is me-pan!
There's so many of them.
There are so many members.
It says "bread" on it.
One of our seniors bought it.
What should we do?
What's on your mind?
What?
Condensed milk... it's cute.
Condensed milk is cute.
Condensed milk is so cute!
Oh, pajamas?
They look like pajamas.
What's yellow? Lemon?
Lemon people.
There's also a shrimp.
Do you have anything that you feel is like you?
Well, I'm the most...
I guess I'd say it's me.
Condensed milk.
Condensed milk is cute.
What do you like, Ryoko?
But I think I like tomatoes.
Tomatoes are cute.
Matching ones are red and blue, reversed.
Oh, here it is.
Oh, nice.
It's nice.
Nice.
This one's cute.
Let's get this one.
Let's buy it and go home.
Let's buy it.
Do you want to take the pants home with you anyway?Would you take your pants home with you anyway?
He said he was taking the wrong pants.
Do you want to take them home with you?
I'll take them with me.
Coding scoop.
No, I'm just so happy we got matching ones.
I'm so happy.
It's the same day together.
Yes, we are.
Wear the same dress.
Let's go.
I'm so happy.
I'm glad.
I'll take a picture when we get here.
I want to post it on my blog.
If I can wear it at the same time every time.
Oh, that's nice.
Then, let's go to Harajuku and take a purikura (purikura is a kind of iron plate).
Let's do Purikura together.
Purikura.
Let's take a purikura together.
I'll take a purikura.
It's been years since I've taken a purikura.
Purikura?
But I actually took one the other day.
Oh, really?
Yes, I did.
Well then...
It's like an event.
Recently?
Recently.
Oh, Purikura.
Then...
I wonder if there are a lot of purikura at Purikura Land.Is there a lot of it in Purikura Land or something?
Yes, probably a lot.
I've been there a few times.
A very long time ago.
Wow, amazing!
Wow!
There are so many!
Amazing!
You can even make a pun.
Wow, which one is good?
It's open!
I'll put it in here!
Oh, it's been so long!
What? Oh, my gosh! Is there such a thing?
Oh, my gosh!
Small face pose!
It looks like a cat pose!
What is it? A cat?
But, you know, it looks really ungodly.
It's very unprofessional!
It makes my eyes unbelievably big.
It's done!
Then!
It looks like this!
I'm so happy!
Yay! Treasure!
Treasure!
I'm so happy!
Hey!
Oh!
Oh! I'm so happy!
I had a great time on our date!
It was fun!It was fun!
Thanks, really!
Thank you so much!
It was so much fun, already!
We were able to buy matching items!
It was a great memory!
It was great!
I really had a great time!
I want to go again with Ryoko to different places!
I would love to!
Thank you all for watching!
Please subscribe to our channel, give us a high rating, and leave a comment!
Thank you very much!
Bye bye!
See you soon!